job-hunt.org 2019-06-22

# The Privacy Policy for Job-Hunt.Org - Job-Hunt.org

By Susan P. Joyce

This Privacy Policy is provided by NETability, Inc. (“us” or “we”), the owner and operator of JOB-HUNT.ORG (the “Site”) in order to clarify our practices regarding the collection, storage, use and disclosure of information gathered by us and the choices available to you regarding the collection and use of your personal information. By visiting the Site, you are confirming that you have read, understood and consent to our practices in collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information.

We are committed to being a trustworthy partner in your job search. You can visit Job-Hunt.Org as often as you want without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.

If you should have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please send an email to SJoyce@netability.com.

### Job-Hunt's Newsletter

For our electronic newsletter, you may provide your name and email address, if you wish to receive it. We use this information to send the Job-Hunt newsletter and other related job search and career information. You may unsubscribe or opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Choice/Opt-Out section below.

To deliver and manage email we send, we use AWeber. AWeber’s [Permission Pledge](http://www.aweber.com/permission.htm) protects your privacy and inbox. 

### Choice/Opt-Out

The Site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. Simply click on the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of a mailing.

You may also send email to SJoyce@netability.com (you will have to clear yourself through our spam filter). More contact information is at the bottom of this page.

### Anti-Spam Policy

We do not send emails to people that do not have a relationship with our company. This relationship can start in the following ways:

The person:

  * Opted in to one of our email lists either at one of our sites or one of our partner sites 
  * Requested a free email course 
  * Filled out an online survey in return for a gift 
  * Entered a drawing or contest either online or in-person at a live event 
  * Purchased a product 
  * Contacted the website  

### Passive Information Collected

**Server Log Files:**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movements from page to page to understand what our visitors like and don't like, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use (e.g. browser used, monitor resolution, etc.). IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Information Collected Actively

**Advertisers/Sponsors:**

We practice transparency in revenue generation. Revenue-generating links are identified as "Advertisement" or "Sponsor" or are across the top of a page or in the column on the right side of Job-Hunt pages.

Advertisers such as Google's AdSense can place ads on Job-Hunt's pages.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to Job-Hunt.  

  * Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on their visit to Job-Hunt and/or other sites on the Internet.  

  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. (Alternatively, opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.)
  * [How Google uses cookies](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies "How Google uses cookies") (https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies) explains Google's process -- the types of cookies used by Google, managing cookies in your browser, how Google retains collected data, and more.

_Please note that the use of ads on the Site enable it to be available for free to all users._

Please be aware that if you use an external link from the Site to an advertiser’s or sponsor’s site (each, a “Sponsor Website”), this Privacy Policy does not apply to any such Sponsor Website. Your browsing or other activities on any third-party website, including those linked to the Site, are subject to such third party’s own rules and policies which may differ from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for any activities and practices by each Sponsor Website, including the information or content provided thereon. By accessing or using the Site, you are agreeing that we are not responsible for, and we do not exercise control over, any third-parties with whom you may come into contact with or engage in a transaction with as a direct or indirect result of your access of use of the Site, including, but not limited to sponsors and advertisers.

### Outside Links:

**This privacy statement applies solely to Job-Hunt.Org.**

The Site contains links to other sites operated by third parties. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

> _We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. Job-Hunt.Org is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Before adding those sites to Job-Hunt's categorized lists of links, each site is evaluated to see if they protect the privacy of their visitors and, particularly, their job applicants. We do not knowingly add sites that treat applicant information casually. However, a site may change its policies and practices after being added to Job-Hunt._

Please read Protecting Your Privacy,  Choosing a Job Site, and our Disclaimer regarding these sites.

### Shared Data:

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers for the purposes of making the Site advertising and other features more contextually relevant or to assist us with the operational aspects of the Site; however, we do not provide these parties with any personal information that can identify a specific individual.

No personally identifiable information (i.e. e-mail addresses of newsletter subscribers) will be intentionally shared with any third party unless such disclosure is required by law or a summons or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is necessary to:

  * Comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, court order or other legal process;
  * Protect the rights, property, and/or safety of the Site, the Site visitors or any other individuals or companies, or the general public;
  * Enforce our Terms of Use or to protect the security or integrity of the Site; and/or
  * Provide supportive services to the Site (see Third Parties, below) or to NETability, Inc.

If we sell our email business, we may also transfer personally identifiable information to the buyer.  

### Third Parties:

Agents of the Site may provide supportive services, such as e-mail list management services for Job-Hunt's newsletter, hosting for the Site, etc. However, these third parties are not allowed to use any information disclosed to them for any purpose other than the support of the Site.

### Cookies:

When you access the Site, we or our third party partners and advertisers may send one or more cookies to your computer. A "cookie" is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. In some circumstances, we use "cookies" to test visitor reactions to some particular aspect of the Site or to track the number of visitors for our advertisers. Our cookies do not collect any personally identifiable information. You can usually modify the security setting of your browser to block or to accept cookies or show an alert when a cookie is being sent. Please be informed that some features of the Site may not function properly if cookies are refused. Check your browser's Help function for more information.

### Notification of Changes:

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

### Governing Law:

This Privacy Policy and the use of this site are governed by the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Any claim related to the site or to this privacy statement shall be brought in a federal or state court in Worcester County, within one year after the claim arises. Users of the Site consent to the jurisdiction of such court as the most convenient and appropriate for the resolution of disputes concerning this Privacy Policy.

### Contact Job-Hunt:

If you have any concerns about your privacy at Job-Hunt or a complaint about inappropriate or infringing content on Job-Hunt or one of the sites listed on Job-Hunt, please contact us:

> Susan Joyce  
>  Job-Hunt.Org  
>  c/o NETability, Inc.  
>  P.O. Box 507  
>  Marlborough, MA 01752-0507

Updated: 10 June 2018

* * *

**About the author...**

Online job search expert Susan P. Joyce has been observing the online job search world and teaching online job search skills since 1995. A veteran of the United States Marine Corps and a recent Visiting Scholar at the MIT Sloan School of Management, Susan is a two-time layoff “graduate” who has worked in human resources at Harvard University and in a compensation consulting firm. Since 1998, Susan has been editor and publisher of Job-Hunt.org. Follow Susan on Twitter at [@jobhuntorg](http://twitter.com/jobhuntorg "@JobHuntOrg") and on [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/JobHuntOrg "Job-Hunt.org on Facebook"), [LinkedIn](https://www.linkedin.com/in/susanjoyce/ "Susan P. Joyce LinkedIn Profile").
